Hi Gabriella, it's Diane Card.
How are you?
Happy New Year.
I wanted to quickly uh call uh because I figured this would be easier than uh texting.
Um but please feel free just to text back if you're busy, or we can um follow up with an email once we decide.
Uh working on the thong and getting that ready to send to Caroline.
Um and I can hit spec on pretty much uh every single thing except for leg opening.
Um and I think it's because the spec that's here is based on um the finished garment.
So I wanted to just make sure and confirm with you because uh uh up until now we've come to the con we've come to the conclusion and agreement that I'm just matching spec on everything, on everything that's there, just match spec because we obviously we have the issues that came through on those first two.
Uh however, this one I I literally just cannot hit the leg hole if I keep the length or the center front length and center back length as well as the waistband.
Um the leg hole is just I can't get it small enough to match spec.
So um I wanted to just basically just get approval from you to just get the leg hole um to be as small as I can while matching the waist and length specs.
Um and uh and then just allowing for Caroline to ease that into the elastic whenever she is sewing.
Uh if you don't mind giving me a text back just saying confirmed and approved or um please just match spec.
I don't I'm not sure how I would even match it, but um I would probably have to change the waist or I don't know.
Anyway, um let me know what your thoughts are.
Uh and I hope you're having a good day.
Bye.